{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "3.4 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000034", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.7 * 10^3", "explanation": "There are 3 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^3 to show that we moved the decimal point 3 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n6700", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.7 * 10^2", "explanation": "There are 2 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^2 to show that we moved the decimal point 2 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n570", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.2 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.082", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.3 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0073", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.3 * 10^3", "explanation": "There are 3 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^3 to show that we moved the decimal point 3 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n4300", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.1 * 10^8", "explanation": "There are 8 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^8 to show that we moved the decimal point 8 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n310000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.1 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000041", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.2 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n3200000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.9 * 10^3", "explanation": "There are 3 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^3 to show that we moved the decimal point 3 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n6900", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.5 * 10^3", "explanation": "There are 3 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^3 to show that we moved the decimal point 3 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n7500", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.3 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00083", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.0 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n2000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.5 * 10^8", "explanation": "There are 8 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^8 to show that we moved the decimal point 8 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n250000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.1 * 10^-8", "explanation": "There are 8 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-8to show that we moved the decimal point 8places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000000011", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.9 * 10^2", "explanation": "There are 2 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^2 to show that we moved the decimal point 2 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n990", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.0 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n30000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.8 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000058", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.8 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n5800000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.8 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000028", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.3 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000053", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.6 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n5600000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.9 * 10^8", "explanation": "There are 8 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^8 to show that we moved the decimal point 8 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n390000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.5 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000085", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.6 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000036", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.2 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n8200000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.6 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n26000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.6 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n16000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.0 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0002", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.2 * 10^-7", "explanation": "There are 7 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-7to show that we moved the decimal point 7places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00000072", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.0 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n500000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.3 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n93000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.5 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0045", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.7 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00017", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.7 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n270000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.0 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00003", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.2 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000072", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.1 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0091", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.9 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n19000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.4 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000044", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.8 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000068", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.3 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n5300000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.1 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000061", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.5 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n5500000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.3 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n63000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.4 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n540000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.6 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0026", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.9 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.019", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.1 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000051", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.2 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000042", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.8 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n3800000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.3 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n13000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.1 * 10^2", "explanation": "There are 2 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^2 to show that we moved the decimal point 2 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n110", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.4 * 10^-8", "explanation": "There are 8 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-8to show that we moved the decimal point 8places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000000054", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.8 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n28000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.8 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0068", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.7 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.047", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.3 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n23000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.4 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.094", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.5 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000045", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.4 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000094", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.7 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00037", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.0 * 10^3", "explanation": "There are 3 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^3 to show that we moved the decimal point 3 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n2000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.2 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n920000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.5 * 10^2", "explanation": "There are 2 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^2 to show that we moved the decimal point 2 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n350", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.9 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n79000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.7 * 10^8", "explanation": "There are 8 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^8 to show that we moved the decimal point 8 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n870000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.9 * 10^2", "explanation": "There are 2 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^2 to show that we moved the decimal point 2 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n990", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.7 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000067", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.4 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n2400000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.2 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0062", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.2 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00052", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.0 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.008", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7.6 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.076", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.6 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00086", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.8 * 10^-4", "explanation": "There are 4 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-4to show that we moved the decimal point 4places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00028", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.9 * 10^-7", "explanation": "There are 7 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-7to show that we moved the decimal point 7places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00000019", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.6 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000066", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.7 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000087", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.2 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000082", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.5 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000085", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.6 * 10^8", "explanation": "There are 8 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^8 to show that we moved the decimal point 8 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n260000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.1 * 10^4", "explanation": "There are 4 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^4 to show that we moved the decimal point 4 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n81000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.5 * 10^-8", "explanation": "There are 8 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-8to show that we moved the decimal point 8places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000000015", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.7 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.067", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.5 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000055", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9.9 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.000099", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.3 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n8300000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4.8 * 10^7", "explanation": "There are 7 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^7 to show that we moved the decimal point 7 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n48000000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2.5 * 10^6", "explanation": "There are 6 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^6 to show that we moved the decimal point 6 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n2500000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.7 * 10^-6", "explanation": "There are 6 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-6to show that we moved the decimal point 6places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0000067", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.1 * 10^-2", "explanation": "There are 2 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-2to show that we moved the decimal point 2places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.051", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.9 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0069", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6.5 * 10^-7", "explanation": "There are 7 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-7to show that we moved the decimal point 7places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00000065", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8.2 * 10^-7", "explanation": "There are 7 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-7to show that we moved the decimal point 7places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00000082", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.7 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n370000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.0 * 10^-5", "explanation": "There are 5 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-5to show that we moved the decimal point 5places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.00005", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3.0 * 10^5", "explanation": "There are 5 digits after the first digit.\n Therefore we place the decimal point after the first digit and add the remaining numbers after.\n Then we add a * 10^5 to show that we moved the decimal point 5 places to theright.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n300000", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "1.7 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.0017", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5.0 * 10^-3", "explanation": "There are 3 zeroes before first nonzero digit.\nWe first write that first nonzero digit and add a decimal point after the digit.\nAdd the remaining digits after the decimal point.\nNow put the * 10^-3to show that we moved the decimal point 3places to the left.", "question": "Express in scientific notation:\n0.005", "type": "text"}
]}